JENNIFER GREGORY



ABOUT

I'm a web development student interested in web design and user experience design. I enjoy stepping into users' shoes to build websites that meet their needs.

I have experience with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, SQL, C#, Angular, ASP.NET, responsive web design, SEO, content management systems (WordPress and Joomla), and Git/GitHub. I'm continuously learning new things to improve my skillset.



EDUCATION

Web Developer AAS Degree | Wake Technical Community College 2019 – 2022

Bachelor of Science in Elementary Education | University of North Carolina at Greensboro



EXPERIENCE

Tutor | Self-Employed

JUNE 2014 - PRESENT

Provides reading and writing tutoring to elementary and middle school-aged students. Key responsibilities include utilizing Orton-Gillingham Evidence-Based Reading Instruction, develops and implements lesson plans to improve reading and writing skills, and conducts weekly assessments to measure skill acquisition.

Nanny | Private Family

AUGUST 2011 - MAY 2014

Provided daily care for two children, ages 2 and 4. At the end of my employment, the children were 4 and 7.



SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Adobe Creative Suite

- JavaScript
- WordPress
- Bootstrap